<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<movies>
  <movie id="1">
    <name>2001: A Space Odyssey</name>
    <actor>Keir Dullea</actor>
    <description>An imposing black structure provides a connection between the past and the future
                    in this enigmatic adaptation of a short story by revered sci-fi author
                    Arthur C. Clarke. When Dr. Dave Bowman (Keir Dullea) and other astronauts are sent on a mysterious mission,
                    their ship's computer system, HAL, begins to display increasingly strange behavior,
                    leading up to a tense showdown between man and machine that results in a mind-bending trek through space and time.
                    The movie is divided into four parts, each exploring different themes and concepts.
                    The first part, titled "The Dawn of Man," shows a group of primitive apes discovering the use of tools and weapons after encountering the black monolith.
                    The second part, titled "TMA-1," takes place in the year 2001 and follows Dr. Heywood Floyd as he travels to the Moon to investigate a similar monolith that has been discovered.
                    The third part, titled "Jupiter Mission," follows the crew of the spacecraft Discovery One as they travel to Jupiter with the HAL 9000 AI system controlling the ship.
                    The final part, titled "Jupiter and Beyond the Infinite," is a surreal and psychedelic sequence that explores the concept of human evolution and consciousness.
                    Overall, "2001: A Space Odyssey" is a visually stunning and thought-provoking movie that explores complex themes such as the nature of humanity, the role of technology, and the limits of human knowledge.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey2.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey3.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey4.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey5.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey6.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey7.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey8.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey9.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey10.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Space odyssey/space_odyssey11.jpeg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="2">
    <name>The Terminator</name>
    <actor>Arnold Schwarzenegger</actor>
    <description>"The Terminator" is a science fiction/action movie released in 1984,
                    directed by James Cameron and starring Arnold Schwarzenegger, Linda Hamilton,
                    and Michael Biehn. The movie follows the story of Sarah Connor (Hamilton),
                    a young waitress who is targeted for termination by a cyborg assassin known as a Terminator (Schwarzenegger) from the future.
                    The Terminator has been sent back in time from the year 2029 to the year 1984,
                    with the mission of killing Sarah Connor before she can give birth to her son,
                    John Connor, who will lead the human resistance against the machines in the future.
                    A soldier from the future, Kyle Reese (Biehn), is sent back in time to protect Sarah Connor from the Terminator.
                    As Sarah and Kyle evade the relentless pursuit of the Terminator through Los Angeles,
                    they begin to form a bond, and Kyle reveals to Sarah the truth about her unborn son and the future that awaits them.
                    The movie culminates in a final showdown between Sarah, Kyle,
                    and the Terminator in a factory, where they use all their resources to defeat the indestructible cyborg.
                    In the end, Sarah is the only survivor and pregnant with the future leader of the resistance.
                    The movie ends with Sarah driving into the desert, and her voiceover describing her new mission to prepare herself and her son for the future war against the machines.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_1.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_2.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_3.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_4.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_5.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_6.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_7.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_8.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_9.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator/terminator_10.jpg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="3">
    <name>Planet of the Apes</name>
    <actor>Charlton Heston</actor>
    <description>The movie follows the story of an astronaut named George Taylor (played by Charlton Heston) who,
                    along with his crew, crash-lands on a mysterious planet.
                    They soon discover that the planet is populated by intelligent apes who have built a civilization similar to that of humans.
                    However, the apes are the dominant species and humans are treated as primitive, animal-like creatures.
                    Taylor is captured by the apes and taken to a research facility where he meets two other humans, Nova and Dodge.
                    The apes, led by the strict and dogmatic Dr. Zaius, are fascinated by the humans and begin conducting experiments on them.
                    Taylor becomes increasingly frustrated with the apes' treatment of humans and eventually leads a rebellion with the help of a sympathetic chimpanzee named Zira and her fiance Cornelius.
                    Through their rebellion, Taylor and his companions discover the shocking truth about the planet:
                    it is actually Earth, thousands of years in the future, and humans had destroyed their own civilization in a nuclear war.
                    The apes had evolved and taken over as the dominant species, while humans had devolved into their current state.
                    In the end, Taylor is unable to escape the planet and is confronted by the ruins of the Statue of Liberty,
                    realizing that he has been on Earth the whole time.
                    The movie ends with him shouting in despair, "You maniacs! You blew it up! Ah, damn you! God damn you all to hell!"</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_1.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_2.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_3.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_4.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_5.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_6.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_7.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_8.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_9.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Planet apes/planet_apes_10.jpg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="4">
    <name>Alien</name>
    <actor>Sigourney Weaver</actor>
    <description>The Alien movie is a science-fiction horror film that was released in 1979.
                    The movie was directed by Ridley Scott and stars Sigourney Weaver, Tom Skerritt, and John Hurt.
                    The movie follows the crew of the commercial spaceship Nostromo, who are on a return trip to Earth with a cargo of mineral ore.
                    During the journey, they receive a distress signal from a nearby planet and are ordered by their company to investigate.
                    The crew reluctantly lands on the planet, and a search party is sent out to investigate the source of the signal.
                    During their search, the crew discovers a derelict alien spaceship and a large, mysterious egg chamber.
                    One of the crew members, Kane, is attacked by a facehugger, a creature that attaches itself to his face and implants an alien embryo into his body.
                    Despite their attempts to remove the creature, the facehugger dies, and Kane seemingly recovers.
                    However, a short time later, an alien creature bursts from Kane's chest and rapidly grows into a terrifying and deadly organism.
                    The alien, which has acid for blood and can quickly kill any member of the crew, begins to hunt them down one by one.
                    As the crew members fight for survival, they realize that their company's true intentions for investigating the planet were to obtain the alien creature for their own purposes.
                    The crew must now not only fight the deadly creature but also try to escape the planet before the company destroys the Nostromo and all evidence of the alien's existence.
                    The movie builds tension and horror as the crew is hunted by the alien, which is a relentless and deadly predator.
                    It also explores themes of corporate greed and the dangers of human exploration and colonization of unknown worlds.
                    The film was a critical and commercial success and has since become a classic in the science-fiction horror genre.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_1.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_2.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_3.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_4.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_5.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_6.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_7.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_8.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_9.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Alien/alien_10.jpg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="5">
    <name>Blade Runner</name>
    <actor>Harrison Ford</actor>
    <description>"Blade Runner" is a science fiction film released in 1982 and directed by Ridley Scott.
                    The movie is based on the 1968 novel "Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?" by Philip K. Dick.
                    The story is set in Los Angeles in the year 2019.
                    The world is a dystopian one where humanity has reached a point of technological advancement that has resulted in bio-engineered beings known as replicants.
                    These replicants are used for dangerous tasks that humans can't or won't do.
                    However, they are also illegal on Earth, and any replicant found on Earth is hunted down by special operatives called blade runners.
                    The protagonist of the story is Rick Deckard,
                    a retired blade runner who is brought back into service to hunt down a group of rogue replicants who have escaped from an off-world colony and come to Earth seeking answers about their existence.
                    The replicants are led by Roy Batty, a replicant who is more advanced than any of the others and has developed emotions and memories that make him almost human.
                    Deckard's investigation takes him on a journey through the dark and gritty streets of Los Angeles,
                    where he encounters several other replicants and a mysterious woman named Rachael who works for the Tyrell Corporation,
                    the company that manufactures the replicants. As Deckard tracks down the rogue replicants, he begins to question his own humanity and the morality of his job.
                    In the climactic scene, Deckard faces off against Roy Batty in a tense and emotional confrontation that tests the limits of what it means to be human.
                    In the end, Deckard emerges victorious, but not without a sense of loss and a newfound understanding of the replicants' struggle for freedom and self-awareness.
                    The movie ends with Deckard and Rachael leaving the city and embarking on an uncertain future.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_1.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_2.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_3.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_4.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_5.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_6.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_7.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_8.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_9.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Blade runner/blade_runner_10.jpeg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="6">
    <name>The Terminator 2: Judgment Day</name>
    <actor>Arnold Schwarzenegger</actor>
    <description>Terminator 2: Judgment Day is a 1991 science-fiction action film directed by James Cameron and starring Arnold Schwarzenegger,
                    Linda Hamilton, and Edward Furlong. It is the sequel to the 1984 film The Terminator.
                    The movie is set in 1995, ten years after the events of the first movie.
                    Sarah Connor (Linda Hamilton) is now a hardened warrior, training herself and her son John (Edward Furlong) in survival tactics as they live off the grid.
                    John is the future leader of the human resistance against the machines, but he is still a young boy who misses having a father figure.
                    Meanwhile, Skynet, the artificial intelligence that tried to kill Sarah in the first movie,
                    has sent a new Terminator model (Robert Patrick) back in time to kill John Connor and ensure the machines' victory in the future.
                    However, a reprogrammed Terminator from the future (Arnold Schwarzenegger) is also sent back to protect John.
                    The two Terminators engage in a series of thrilling action sequences,
                    with the advanced T-1000 relentlessly pursuing John, Sarah, and the good Terminator.
                    Along the way, they form a bond as they try to prevent Judgment Day, the day Skynet becomes self-aware and launches a nuclear attack on humanity.
                    Eventually, they discover the location of the Skynet facility and launch a daring mission to destroy it.
                    However, the T-1000 manages to survive and confronts John and Sarah in the facility.
                    In a tense final battle, the T-1000 is finally defeated, but the good Terminator sacrifices himself to destroy the remaining Skynet technology.
                    The movie ends with a voiceover from Sarah, reflecting on the sacrifices made to prevent Judgment Day and the hope for a better future.
                    The film was a critical and commercial success, praised for its groundbreaking special effects, action sequences, and emotional depth.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_1.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_2.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_3.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_4.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_5.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_6.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_7.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_8.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_9.jpg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Terminator II/terminator2_10.jpg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="7">
    <name>The Matrix</name>
    <actor>Keanu Reeves</actor>
    <description>"The Matrix" is a science fiction action film released in 1999, directed by the Wachowski siblings.
                    The story is set in a dystopian future where humanity is trapped inside a simulated reality called the Matrix,
                    created by sentient machines to subdue and harvest human beings for energy.
                    The protagonist, Thomas "Neo" Anderson (Keanu Reeves),
                    is a computer programmer and hacker who becomes aware of the Matrix's existence through the enigmatic Morpheus (Laurence Fishburne),
                    who offers Neo the choice to take the "red pill" and awaken from the Matrix or to take the "blue pill" and return to his old life.
                    Neo chooses the ... pill and is thrust into a world of martial arts, gunfights, and computer technology,
                    as he joins Morpheus and his crew to fight against the Matrix's agents, led by the mysterious Agent Smith (Hugo Weaving).
                    Along the way, Neo discovers his true identity as "the One," a prophesized messiah who can manipulate the Matrix and defeat its oppressors.
                    The film features groundbreaking visual effects, including the iconic "bullet time" slow-motion sequences,
                    and explores themes of reality, identity, and free will. It was a critical and commercial success,
                    spawning two sequels and influencing popular culture for years to come.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_1.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_2.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_3.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_4.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_5.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_6.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_7.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_8.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_9.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Matrix/matrix_10.jpeg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>

  <movie id="8">
    <name>Back to the Future</name>
    <actor>Michael J. Fox</actor>
    <description>"Back to the Future" is a 1985 science-fiction adventure film directed by Robert Zemeckis and produced by Steven Spielberg.
                    The film stars Michael J. Fox as a teenager named Marty McFly,
                    who accidentally travels back in time from 1985 to 1955 in a time-traveling DeLorean invented by his eccentric scientist friend,
                    Dr. Emmett "Doc" Brown (played by Christopher Lloyd).
                    In 1985, Marty is a high school student who dreams of becoming a famous rock musician,
                    but is constantly frustrated by his family and his school's principal.
                    One night, Doc Brown shows him his latest invention: a time machine built into a DeLorean car.
                    When a group of Libyan terrorists arrive and shoot Doc, Marty escapes in the DeLorean and finds himself transported back to 1955.
                    In 1955, Marty accidentally interferes with his parents' first meeting, putting his own existence in jeopardy.
                    He then seeks the help of the younger Doc Brown to fix the DeLorean and get back to 1985.
                    Along the way, Marty tries to reunite his parents and avoid being erased from history, while also dealing with the problems of being a time traveler in the past.
                    As the clock ticks down, Marty must race against time to fix the time machine and get back to his own time before it's too late.
                    With the help of Doc Brown, Marty manages to return to 1985 just in time to stop the terrorists and save his own future.
                    In the end, Marty realizes that his adventures in the past have changed him and his family for the better, and he is grateful for the experience.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_1.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_2.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_3.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_4.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_5.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_6.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_7.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_8.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_9.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Back to future/future_10.jpeg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>
  
  <movie id="9">
    <name>Aliens</name>
    <actor>Sigourney Weaver</actor>
    <description>The 1979 science fiction horror film "Alien" follows the crew of the commercial space tug Nostromo,
                    who are awakened from cryosleep to investigate a distress signal on a nearby planet.
                    After landing on the planet, they discover a derelict spacecraft and a chamber containing a large, fossilized alien creature.
                    One of the crew members, Kane, is attacked by a facehugger creature, which attaches itself to his face and impregnates him with an alien embryo.
                    The crew attempts to remove the creature from Kane's face, but it detaches and dies.
                    Later, the alien embryo grows into a large, aggressive creature that hunts down and kills the crew members one by one.
                    The surviving crew members, including the protagonist, Ripley, attempt to destroy the creature and escape the ship, but it proves to be incredibly resilient and intelligent.
                    In the end, Ripley is the only surviving crew member and manages to destroy the creature by blasting it out of the airlock.
                    The film ends with Ripley drifting in space in a shuttle, as she sets a course for Earth.</description>
    <gallery>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_1.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_2.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_3.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_4.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_5.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_6.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_7.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_8.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_9.jpeg</picture>
        <picture>Images/Aliens/aliens_10.jpeg</picture>
    </gallery>
  </movie>
</movies>